Hello and welcome to Halmstad University!
Fun to see you!
Come on and I'll show you around a bit.
We start with a little detour right away, come here!
Hi Victoria, fun to see you!
Hi Timmie, the same!
Can't you tell those who watch.
Who are you and what do you do?
Absolutely
Victoria is my name, and works as a study and career counselor here at the university.
I often have guidance calls with students who are interested in-
-To Start studying here at Halmstad University.
But also with students who are already reading here with us.
There will be a lot of questions about admission, eligibility-
-and what you can do after reading a program-
-If the labor market and career and such issues.
You sit with some others who are also sitting in here.
Can you tell us a little more what you all do?
Exactly, it's not just us, study counselors sitting here-
Now we will change shoes a little quickly.
These are special shoes for getting-
-Go into this lab.
So come along now.
This then Electronics Center Halland.
Here we have two pieces of chambers where you measure-
-Electromagnetic fields in different ways.
And we will now go into a chamber called Maxwell.
This is what it looks like in this chamber-
-And here students can measure, wireless, electronics structures.
And as you can see, there are plates on the walls and roof-
-In ordinary cases should students close the door to measure-
-The constructions in here.
So if there is something you want to do and study at Halmstad University.
This is the second chamber.
In this little box you can measure and connect electronics products-
-And see how they can affect the electricity grid.
This chamber is called the noisy chamber.
Compared to the chamber we were in before where it is more quiet.
Here happens and a little more stuff that can ...
... then tests and measures how ...
... electricity products and the fields then affect other things.
Incredibly awesome.
Now we go past the design studio and here are students-
-Movemented children and adolescents in Halland.
This is among the newest we have here at Halmstad University.
Join us for now we will go into the new cafe.
Now we are in the cafe.
The newest cafe we have here in Hus S.
Here you as a student can buy both moderate lunches-
-To some good snacks in the afternoon.
They have incredibly beautiful and study -friendly environments here.
Now we will go into Fab Lab.
So now we are in Fab Lab here.
Hi Tim.
Hey Hey.
-The sports center like a gym located on campus.
It is Eleiko certified and is located in the university's premises.
A great opportunity for you as a student-
-Exercising close to your studies.
One floor up here is one for a cafe.
We have several cafes here on campus, to buy some snacks.
Come and we will end this hike.
Now we have made a proper tour here at Campus-
-I hope you've got to see what it looks like here-
-But there is of course so much more to discover.
I look forward to you looking for an education here-
-At Halmstad University.
So maybe we will even be seen this fall.